Mss.530.1.Ar2
American Philosophical Society
- I. Papers
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1941; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (10 pages); Fokker, A. D., (Adriaan Daniel), 1887-1972 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 11)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 9 letters, 1925-1955.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 6 letters, 1919-1920, 1955.
  - Lecture course on radioactivity, Leiden, 1915-1916; 19.0 leaves.; Fokker, A. D., (Adriaan Daniel), 1887-1972; Kramers, Hendrik Anthony, 1894-1952 (Reel 25, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 21 October 1918 - 8 August 1921; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Foote, Paul D., (Paul Darwin), 1888-1971 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 23 March 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Foote, Paul D., (Paul Darwin), 1888-1971 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letters to J. H. Van Vleck, 24 March 1924 - 10 December 1925; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Foote, Paul D., (Paul Darwin), 1888-1971 (Reel 49, Reel-frame 6)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 2 letters, 1924-1926.
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1900-1924; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (27 pages); Föppl, Aug., (August), 1854-1924 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 12)
  - The Environment and Practice of Atomic Physics in Weimar Germany: A Study in the History of Science, 1967; 1.0 Reel(s); Forman, Paul (Reel AHQP/P-7)
    Ph.D. dissertation, University of California, Berkeley.
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 7 April 1925 - 10 April 1930; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Fortrat, Rene, 1886-1966 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 3, Reel 62, Reel 60, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 2 May 1928 - 12 June 1928; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Foster, John Stuart, 1890-1944 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 13 August 1924; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Foster, John Stuart, 1890-1944 (Reel 12, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Toshio Takamine, 31 July 1923; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Foster, John Stuart, 1890-1944 (Reel 34, Reel-frame 6)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 26 letters, 1923-1958.
  - Letter to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Fournier, G., (Georges) (Reel 65, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 27 October 1913 - 13 June 1922; 13.0 Item(s) 13 letters (32 pages); Fowler, A., (Alfred), 1868-1940 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 18 December 1923 - 15 January 1924; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Fowler, A., (Alfred), 1868-1940 (Reel 60, Reel-frame 1-2)
  - Letter to Alfred Landé, 8 July 1924; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Fowler, A., (Alfred), 1868-1940 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 16)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 5 letters, 1923-1926.
    Royal Society Library, London, England. 17 letters, 1904-1925.
    Deutsche Staatsbibliothek, Berlin, Germany. Material at present held at the Westdeutschen Bibliothek, Marburg/Lahn, Germany. Letters to Heinrich Kayser, 3 letters, 1909-l913. (Darmstaedter Collection, Fic. 1910).
  - Letters to David Mathias Dennison, 12 September 1926 - 27 February 1927; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (4 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 59, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 14 March 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to Werner Heisenberg, 30 November 1933 - 17 July 1934; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 45, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Edwin C. Kemble, 11 November 1925 - 13 July 1937; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (8 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9, Reel 51, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 13 October 1925 - 10 December 1925; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (10 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 8, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Ralph Kronig, 26 May 1925 - 6 April 1929; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (11 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 16, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 28 May 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (3 pages); Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 13)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 46 letters, 1923-1938.
    Rutherford Collection, Cavendish Laboratory, Cambridge, England. Undated letters from Copenhagen; Princeton, New Jersey; University of California; Iowa.
    Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Correspondence with Oswald Veblen, 1922-1928.
    Duke University Archives, Durham, North Carolina. 2 letters to Fritz London, 1929-1930.
  - Lecture course, "Dynamical Theory of Gases (Elementary)," Trinity College, 1922-1923; 52.0 p.; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944; Thomas, L. H., (Llewellyn Hilleth), 1903-1992 (Reel 5, Reel-frame 5)
  - Lecture course, "Thermodynamics and Statistical Mechanics," Trinity College, 1922-1923; 74.0 p.; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944; Thomas, L. H., (Llewellyn Hilleth), 1903-1992 (Reel 5, Reel-frame 6)
  - Lecture course, "The Quantum Theory of Spectra," Cavendish, 1923-1924; 97.0 p.; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944; Thomas, L. H., (Llewellyn Hilleth), 1903-1992 (Reel 5, Reel-frame 2)
  - Lecture course, "Recent Developments of Quantum Theory," Trinity College, 1925; 71.0 p.; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944; Thomas, L. H., (Llewellyn Hilleth), 1903-1992 (Reel 5, Reel-frame 4)
  - Lecture course, "The Quantum Theory", Circa 1924-1926; 45.0 p.; Dirac, P. A. M., (Paul Adrien Maurice), 1902-1984; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 36, Reel-frame 8)
  - Lecture course, "Recent Developments", 1925; 33.0 p.; Dirac, P. A. M., (Paul Adrien Maurice), 1902-1984; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 36, Reel-frame 8)
  - Lectures, "Spinning Electrons", 1926; 8.0 p.; Dirac, P. A. M., (Paul Adrien Maurice), 1902-1984; Fowler, R. H., (Ralph Howard), 1889-1944 (Reel 36, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letter to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Fraenkel, Abraham Adolf, 1891-1965 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter regarding Samuel Sambursky, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Fraenkel, Abraham Adolf, 1891-1965 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1904; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (3 pages); Frahm, Hermann (Reel 30, Reel-frame 13)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 24 October 1920 - 23 December 1922; 16.0 Item(s) 16 letters (38 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Walther Gerlach, May 1921 - 23 April 1923; 10.0 Item(s) 10 letters (15 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel 19, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 23 March 1927 - 17 June 1927; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 2, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter to Edwin C. Kemble, 19 December 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 31 July 1924; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel 8, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 21 December 1919 - 9 January 1920; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 16)
    University of Chicago Library, Chicago, Illinois. Special Collections, James Franck Papers, 1882-1966, 20 linear feet.
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Neils Bohr, 23 letters, 1923-1948.
    Library of the Swedish Academy, Stockholm, Sweden. Letter to C. W. Oseen, 1928.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 2 letters, 1921-1952.
    Duke University Archives, Durham, North Carolina. 2 letters to Fritz London, 1930-1947.
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 18 June 1913; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Franck, James, 1882-1964; Hertz, Gustav, 1887-1975 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 13)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Frank, Nathaniel Herman, 1903-1984 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 13)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1950; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (4 pages); Franz, Walter, 1911-1992 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 13)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1950; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (6 pages); Frauenfelder, Hans, 1922- (Reel 12, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Charles Galton Darwin, 16 March 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (4 pages); Frenkel, Yakov Il'ich, 1894-1952 (Reel 36, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 8 March 1928 - 22 November 1931; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (14 pages); Frenkel, Yakov Il'ich, 1894-1952 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 14)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. 4 letters to Niels Bohr, 1936.
  - Letter to Adalbert Rubinowicz, 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Frerichs, Rudolf, 1901-1982 (Reel 17, Reel-frame B)
  - Letter to Alfred Landé, 1919; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (3 pages); Freundlich, B. (Reel 4, Reel-frame 16)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 26 October 1914 - 29 September 1920; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (26 pages); Fricke, Hugo, 1892-1972 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 4)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 5 letters, 1924-1927.
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1907-1908; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (14 pages); Fricke, Robert, 1861-1930 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 14)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1938; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Frisch, Otto Robert, 1904-1979 (Reel 9, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letter to Erwin Schrödinger, 1946; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Fröbe-Kapteyn, Olga (Reel 37, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Fröhlich, H., (Herbert), 1905-1991 (Reel 9, Reel-frame 11)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 28 April 1924 - 21 July 1927; 7.0 Item(s) 7 letters (10 pages); Fues, Erwin Richard, 1893-1970 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1936-1944; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (6 pages); Fues, Erwin Richard, 1893-1970 (Reel 30, Reel-frame 14)
  - Memoirs of 1925-1927 concerning Erwin Schrödinger and the wave equation, 1963; 30.0 p.; Fues, Erwin Richard, 1893-1970 (Reel 66, Reel-frame 8)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 2 letters, 1930-1932.
    Duke University Archives, Durham, North Carolina. Letters to Fritz London, 5 letters, 1928.
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1946; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Fürth, R., (Reinhold), 1893--1979 (Reel 12, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Edwin C. Kemble, 1932; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (6 pages); Gaboury, G. N. (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Edwin C. Kemble, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Galbraith, Alan Stuart (Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letters to Werner Heisenberg, 15 February 1934 - 28 February 1934; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (9 pages); Gamow, George, 1904-1968 (Reel 45, Reel-frame 2)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 64 letters, 1928-1961.
    Rutherford Collection, Cavendish Laboratory, Cambridge, England. Letters to Ernest Rutherford, 1933-1937.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Correspondence with Albert Einstein, 4 letters, 1946-1948.
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1927-1942; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (7 pages); Gans, Richard, 1880-1954 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 19 January 1914; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (5 pages); Garbasso, Antonio, 1871-1933 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1946; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gärtner, Erna (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1942-1945; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (6 pages); Geendert (Reel 12, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 12 October 1913 - 14 May 1920; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Geiger, Hans, 1882-1945 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
    Bohr Collection, Copenhagen, Denmark. Letters to Niels Bohr, 3 letters, 1925-1931.
    Rutherford Collection, Cavendish Laboratory, Cambridge, England. Letters to Ernest Rutherford, 1912-1937.
    Deutsche Staatsbibliothek, Berlin, Germany. Material at present held at the Westdeutschen Bibliothek, Marburg/Lahn, Germany. Letter to Max Iklé, 1914; 2 letters to Wiedemann, 1912-1915. (Darmstaedter Collection, Fla 1905).
    Deutsches Museum, Munich, Germany. 3 letters to Mitscherlich, 1933-1935.
    Einstein Collection, Princeton, New Jersey. Letter to Albert Einstein, 1921.
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 1919; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Geitler, Jozef, (Jozef Karl Franz Otto Ritter) (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Erwin Schrödinger, 1956; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gell-Mann, Murray (Reel 37, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1949; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Genootschap voor Wetenschappelijke Philosophie. (Reel 12, Reel-frame 12)
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1935-1941; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Gentile, Giovannino, 1906-1942 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1924; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gentofte. (Denmark) (Reel 8, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 8 February 1922 - 22 February 1922; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 9 January 1927 - 18 July 1929; 8.0 Item(s) 8 letters (14 pages); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 5, Reel-frame 1, Reel 62, Reel-frame 3, Reel 61, Reel-frame 1-3)
  - Draft of reply to Fritz Haber's letter of August 4, 1922, 1.0 Item(s); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 19, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 19 July 1923 - 12 April 1924; 8.0 Item(s) 8 letters (16 pages); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Edgar Meyer, 4 November 1921; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 19, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Heinrich Rubens, 5 May 1921; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 19, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Arnold Sommerfeld, 22 May 1922 - 1 September 1926; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (8 pages); Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Memoirs, "Die entscheidenden Stufen für den Nachweis der Richtungsquantelung" [The crucial stages for the proof of direction quantization], 1963; 3.0 p.; Gerlach, Walther, 1889-1979 (Reel 66, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1937; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Germany. Auswärtiges Amt. (Reel 29, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1946-1947; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (6 pages); Gerritsen, Alexander Nicolaas (Reel 12, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 29 October 1920 - 3 December 1920; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (12 pages); Gerthsen, Christian, 1894-1956 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1920; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gesellschaft Telefunken. (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1938; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Ghosh, M. K. (Reel 10, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 1930-1931; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Gibbs, R.C., (Roswell Clifton), b. 1878 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 4, Reel 65, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to Edwin C. Kemble, 1929-1936; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Gibbs, R.C., (Roswell Clifton), b. 1878 (Reel 51, Reel-frame 6, Reel 53, Reel-frame 9)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 1947; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gibbs, R.C., (Roswell Clifton), b. 1878 (Reel 12, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letters to Allen Goodrich Shenstone, 1928; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Gibbs, R.C., (Roswell Clifton), b. 1878 (Reel 59, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 1930-1931; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Gilles, J. (Reel 64, Reel-frame 6, Reel 65, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 1922; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Glaser, Ludwig (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 1920-1921; 5.0 Item(s) 5 letters (10 pages); Glocker, R. (Reel 4, Reel-frame 16)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Glocker, R. (Reel 31, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1913; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (6 pages); Goldstein, Eugen, 1850-1930 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 1943; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gombás, P., (Pál), 1909-1971 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Samuel Abraham Goudsmit, 6 April 1922; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Götze, Raimund (Reel 60, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 2 October 1921; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (4 pages); Götze, Raimund (Reel 31, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to P. A. M. Dirac, 20 January 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gordon, Walter, 1893-1939; Kudar, Johann (Reel 59, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 2 May 1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Gordon, Walter, 1893-1939 (Reel 10, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Alfred Landé, 11 January 1923; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (4 pages); Gordon, Walter, 1893-1939 (Reel 4, Reel-frame 16)
  - Letter to Erwin Schrödinger, 28 September 1926; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gordon, Walter, 1893-1939 (Reel 41, Reel-frame 7)
    Library of the Swedish Academy, Stockholm, Sweden. Letter to C. W. Oseen, 1939.
  - Letters to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 15 July 1930 - 1946; 12.0 Item(s) 12 letters (26 pages); Gorter, C. J., (Cornelius Jacobus), 1907-1980 (Reel 10, Reel-frame 2, Reel 12, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter to Arnold Sommerfeld, 31 December 1935; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Gorter, C. J., (Cornelius Jacobus), 1907-1980 (Reel 31, Reel-frame 2)
    Duke University Archives, Durham, North Carolina. Letters to Fritz London, 7 letters, 1934-1952.
  - Letter to Niels Bohr, 1919; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (6 pages); Goucher, Frederick Shand, 1888-1973 (Reel BSC 2, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Herbert Stanley Allen, 1 November 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Ernst Back, Spring 1927 - 2 November 1930; 8.0 Item(s) 8 letters (16 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 1, Reel 63, Reel-frame 5-6, Reel-frame 7, Reel 64, Reel-frame 4-6)
  - Letters to Niels Bohr, 22 July 1927 - Circa May 1933; 4.0 Item(s) 4 letters (6 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 4, Reel 64, Reel-frame 6, Reel 65, Reel-frame 8, Reel 61, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to Gregory Breit, 7 July 1930 - 29 May 1931; 8.0 Item(s) 8 letters (14 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 5-6, Reel 65, Reel-frame 1-3)
  - Letters to Leon Brillouin, 2 January 1929 - 6 May 1931; 6.0 Item(s) 6 letters (7 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 3, Reel 63, Reel-frame 1-3, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Keivin Burns, 1932; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to H. B. G. Casimir, 11 January 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Sydney Chapman, 1928-1929; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 3, Reel 62, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to K. T. Compton, 13 February 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Heber Doust Curtis, Circa 1932-1933; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 8)
  - Letters to Charles Galton Darwin, 1 May 1929 - 28 August 1931; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (16 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 4, Reel 65)
  - Letter to Dean of Faculty of Science, University of Cairo, 1928; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to A. M. I. A. W. Durnford, 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter to Carl Eckart, 18 December 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letters to Paul Ehrenfest, 29 December 1926 - Circa 24 March 1930; 5.0 Item(s) 4 letters (11 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 2, Reel 60, Reel-frame 9, Reel 64, Reel-frame 2-3, Reel 63, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Alexander Ellett, 1930; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 1-2)
  - Letter to Enrico Fermi, 26 March 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to A. D. Fokker, 1927; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letters to John Stuart Foster, 7 May 1928 - 5 July 1928; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (5 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 2-3)
  - Letter to Alfred Fowler, 24 December 1928; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to R. H. Fowler, 12 March 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Abraham Adolf Fraenkel, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letter to James Franck, 1927; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to Walther Gerlach, 7 June 1928 - 13 July 1929; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (5 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 2-3, Reel 63, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letters to R. C. Gibbs, 1930-1931; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 4, Reel 65, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to J. Gilles, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Jerome Bowles Green, 25 November 1929 - 27 November 1929; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (3 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 7)
  - Letter to W. de Groot, 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Wander Johannes de Haas, 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to Edward Lee Hill, 28 September 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Arthur Llewelyn Hughes, 16 July 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 5)
  - Letter to David Rittenhouse Inglis, 1931; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 4)
  - Letter to S. B. Ingram, 1929; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 63, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letters to International Education Board, 1927; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 61, Reel-frame 2)
  - Letter to Edwin C. Kemble, 31 January 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Carl Clarence Kiess, 1928; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 62, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to W. S. Klein, 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (1 page); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 6)
  - Letter to Harold P. Knauss, 1930; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letter to Hendrik Anthony Kramers, 9 February 1939; 1.0 Item(s) 1 letter (2 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 10, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to Alfred Landé, 12 November 1923 - 12 May 1927; 13.0 Item(s) 13 letters (31 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 6, Reel-frame 1)
  - Letters to F. W. Loomis, 4 May 1931 - 13 May 1931; 2.0 Item(s) 2 letters (4 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 65, Reel-frame 3)
  - Letters to Julian Ellis Mack, 5 March 1928 - 9 December 1930; 3.0 Item(s) 3 letters (3 pages); Goudsmit, Samuel Abraham, 1902-1978 (Reel 64, Reel-frame 6, Reel-frame 1, Reel 62)